怎么回事  为什么这里这么冷
Is it just me, or is it really cold in here?
既然如此  何妨你再套件衣服呢
Well, here. Why don't you wear this?
你的队服
Your letterman jacket?
是啊  哦
Yeah. Oh.
你不是说你觉得有点冷么
You said you were cold.
是啊
I did. I am.
呃  有点冷
Brr. Cold.
一会见了  鲁尼
Well, later, Rooney.
我那双闪亮的
Do my crystal-clear
绿色大眼睛没有骗我吧
Emerald-green eyes deceive me
迪吉把他的队服给你了
Or did Diggie just give you his letterman jacket?
恭喜啦
con-graz-ulations.
好吧  淡定  丽芙
Okay, simmer down, Liv.
我只是觉得有点冷  这又没什么
I was just cold. It doesn't mean anything.
他这不是明摆着喜欢你么
It's so obvi he likes you, Maddie.
我知道他喜欢我  不过你觉得他真的这么喜欢我么
I know he likes me, but do you think he like like likes me?
我想我应该知道  但我到底该怎么才能完全知道
I think I know, but how do I like know know?
他这不是把它的外套给你了么
Well, he gave you his coat coat.
或许你劈头盖脸的
Maybe he's just confused as to how you feel
“别来无恙”“有点事”
With all the "s'ups" and the "stuffs"
和“哈  怎样”让他看不清他对你的感情
And the "bam whats" flying at him.
他能坚持这么久不离你而去已经算是一个奇迹了
It's honestly amazing that he stuck around this long.
你早该告诉他你喜欢他了
Just tell him you like him already.
丽芙 我不知道
I don't know, Liv.
我觉得我和迪吉这样并无大碍啊
I think Diggie and I are fine the way we are.
你怎么会觉得每当我和迪吉面对面气氛都
I mean, you're acting like every time we see each other
尴尬异常啊
It's completely awkward.
嘿  鲁尼
Hey, Rooney.
我的皮夹还在这件衣服的口袋里
Just forgot my wallet in my jacket.
这
Oh.
给你
Here you go.
谢了
Thank you.
- 别来无恙  - 有点事
- S'up? - Stuff.
哈  怎样
Bam, what?
你觉得他“有点事”该怎么理解
So what do you think he meant by "stuff"?
最好的朋友
Better in stereo
不同的朋友
B— b-- better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
- I'm up with the sunshine -let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
- I lace up my high tops - oh no
扣篮  热热身
- slam dunk - ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
- I'm under the spotlight - holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
I'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go, go, go
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the other half of me, me
学不来的朋友
the half I'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the better half of me, me
离不开的朋友
the half I'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.
欢迎各位
Welcome...
从宇宙的另一头
From across the void of space
来到火箭社
To rocketry club.
火箭社是由一群有建造
Rocketry club is for people with such diverse interests
发射和讨论模型火箭
As building rockets, launching rockets
这些特殊兴趣爱好的人组成
And talking about rockets.
对了  我们有时候还会设计
Ooh, we also occasionally draw rockets
有朝一日我们能建造  发射和讨论的火箭
We hope to one day build, launch and talk about.
火箭社成员们
Fellow rocketeers,
我向各位介绍
I present to you
眼镜蛇 XT 火箭
The Viper XT.
嘿  乔伊
Hey, joey.
这水瓶火箭真不错啊  哈
Nice bottle rocket. Burn!
哦
Oh!
火箭社最大的问题
The problem with rocketry club
就是我的死对头  亚蒂
Is my archnemesis Artie.
对 你没听错
Yeah, that's right.
我有个死对头
I have an archnemesis.
我多少也算是个大人物
I'm kind of a big deal.
该被嘲笑的是你吧  亚蒂
The burn is on you, Artie.
眼镜蛇 XT 火箭能进一步巩固我在火箭社的地位
The Viper XT solidifies my rocketry club dominance.
你们都应该叫我火箭大王  哈
You can call me the rocket king. Wah!
我相信火箭大王的称号
Oh, I believe the title of rocket king
应该是我的
Is mine.
各位注意
Behold.
这是鹰式 500 型火箭
The Falcon 500.
呼  快来看  哥们
Ooh, check it, my homies.
你们超级酷的妈妈刚换了一台最新的智能手机
Your supercool mom just got the newest smartphone.
天啊  就是握着它都让我感觉很智能  唔
Yep. Just holding it makes me feel smart. Whoo!
这玩意闪光灯还挺厉害的
Pretty strong flash on this baby.
也许你们俩小伙子可以教我
Maybe you boys could show me
一些更加复杂的软件系统
Some of the more sophisticated a.P.P.S.
那好  现在教你第一课
Well, here's your first lesson,
“超级酷的妈妈”
"supercool mom."
宅男们都管它叫“应用”
The homies pronounce it "apps."
酷  你安装了面对面聊天的应用
Cool! You've got facegab.
这是我和我的朋友
That's a video chat.
用来视频对话的
I use it with all my friends.
除了西蒙  他一般都在挖鼻孔
Except simon. He picks his nose,
我可不需要看那么仔细
And I don't need to see that up close.
好了  给我  我来教你怎么呼叫丽芙
Okay, here. I'll show you how to call Liv.
你点击这儿  拨打她的号码
You click here, dial her number,
希望她不要发觉这是你
Hope she doesn't realize it's you
然后就会拒绝接听
And decide not to answer.
你好
Hello?
噢  你好  丽芙
Oh! Hey. Hello, Liv.
我是你妈妈
It's mom.
猜猜我是在哪里跟你聊天呢
Guess where I'm calling you from?
我就猜是厨房吧
I'm going to go with kitchen,
因为我看得到你
Because I can see you...
坐在厨房里
Sitting in the kitchen.
嘿  你床边那个不是我们的
Hey. Is that our hip-hop sno-cone maker
说唱兼果味冰淇淋机么
Beside your bed?
呃  什么冰淇淋机来着
Uh, what sno-cone maker?
哪来的床
What bed?
你到底是谁
Who are you?
她们敢偷我们的冰淇淋机  吃了豹子胆吧
How dare they steal our sno-cone maker?
我们快去把“臭蛋阵风”救出来吧
Let's go rescue the notorious s.N.O.
亲爱的 除虫师告诉我了个坏消息
Bad news from the exterminator, hon.
我们家有不少名叫食木粉蠹的甲虫
We've got wood-eating powder post beetles.
噢  我奶奶的老房子有这家伙
Oh. My grandmother had those in her old house.
我从来没见过那个房子啊
I never saw that house.
正是如此
Exactly.
除虫师需要来彻底清查我们的房子
They need to tent our place.
我们得把不想沾上杀虫剂的东西都打包
We've got to pack up anything we don't want pesticide on
这个周末搬出去住
And clear out for the weekend.
哦
Ooh.
我想去麦迪逊度假直至整个周末结束
I'm thinking a last minute weekend getaway to madison
因此我们就可以游泳  购物
So we can swim, shop,
玩乐  血拼还有大采购
Play, shop and shop.
但是
But...
这个计划必须保密
This has to be a secret.
一旦丽芙发现了我们房子里有虫子
If Liv finds out we have bugs,
她就会吓疯的
She will freak out.
丽芙对虫子可是恐惧至极
Oh, Liv has an irrational fear of bugs.
当她还很小的时候  我给她读了《夏洛的网》
When she was little, I read her the first three pages
开头三页  然后她昏过去了
Of "charlotte's web" and she passed out.
上周  丽芙正在洗澡
Last week, Liv was in the shower.
她看见了一只瓢虫
She saw a ladybug and...
结果这事就发生了
This happened.
后来发现那不是一只瓢虫
Turns out it wasn't a ladybug.
那只是软糖豆
It was a jelly bean.
我从来都不知道我头发里有什么
I never know what's in my hair
直到我彻底洗一遍
Until I rinse it out.
唔  橘子味的
Ooh, tangerine.
所以我要上网
So I'm gonna go on the internet
给咱们预订酒店房间
And make us a hotel reservation
这就要用到我炫酷的新手机  真是步入未来了啊
With my fab new phone. The future is now.
啊呀呀  我不喜欢未来
Oh, I don't like the future.
我们看到冰淇淋机了  交出来
We saw the sno-cone maker. Hand it over.
你们是不会找到的
you'll never find it.
我找到了
I found it.
柠檬 椰子
lemon, coconut
草莓 酸橙
strawberry, lime
你做冰淇淋我唱歌
you make a sno-cone while I rhyme
吼  吼  吼  吼
ho ho ho ho
谁想来点果味冰淇淋
who wants a sno-cone?
现在你们明白为啥我们要把它藏起来了吧
And you wonder why we hid it from you.
喔 老妈又想视频聊天
Oh, it's mom facegabbing again.
她也许是一不小心拨了我的号
She probably doesn't even know she called me.
能离开这房子真是太激动了
I'm kind of excited to get out of this house.
我早已准备好改头换面了
I'm so ready for a change.
- 离开这房子  - 嘘
- Out of the house? - Shh.
调成静音
and mute.
现在我们听得到他们  而他们听不到我们
Now we can hear them, but they can't hear us.
“改头换面”是什么意思
What does "ready for a change" mean?
这不是很明显么  他们想赶你走
Isn't it obvious? They want to get rid of you.
嘘
Shh.
把所有东西打包
This is such a pain to pack everything up
再搬出房子真是痛苦啊
And move out of the house.
听起来像是他们卖了房子带我们搬家
It sounds like they sold the house and we're moving.
搬家  不不不  这肯定不对劲
Moving? No, that can't be right.
我知道孩子们会抱怨
I know the kids are gonna complain
离开他们的伙伴们
About missing their friends,
但是他们会喜欢上麦迪逊的
But they're gonna love madison.
麦迪逊
Madison?!
麦迪逊可是两小时车程以外的地方
Madison's two hours from here.
我们要进完全不同的一个学校
That's a completely different school
没有迪吉在里边
With no Diggies in it.
明天 4 点我们要带上行李离开这儿
We have to be packed up and out of here by 4:00 tomorrow.
明天
Tomorrow?!
他们怎么可能搬家了还不告诉我们？
How could they not tell us we're moving?
哇哦
Wow.
明天就是我们在斯蒂文角的最后一天了
Tomorrow's our last day in Stevens Point.
不可理喻
Unacceptable.
妈  爸
Mom, dad,
我们听到了
We heard you.
哪儿来的声音？
What's that noise?
是你的孩子们
It's your children.
就是关于麦迪逊你还没咨询那群人
The ones you didn't consult about madison.
哦
Oh.
手机还开着
the phone was on?
破软件
Stupid a.P.P.S
孩子们  我们怕你们若听到消息
Guys, we thought you'd freak out less
都会精神崩溃的
If we surprised you with the news.
那么  我们现在崩溃了
Well, we're freaking.
你必须把这计划取消了
You have to call this off.
抱歉  该付的都已经付了
Sorry. Everything's paid for.
我们刚达成了一个完美的协议
We just got a really sweet deal.
这实在太过分了
This is an outrage.
把泳衣也带上  那里有个游泳池哦
Pack your swimsuits. There's a pool.
唔  作为墙头草  我改支持他们了
Ooh, game changer. I'm in.
天啊
Wow.
我们这是真的要搬家了
We are really moving.
是啊  这是我们在这里的最后一天
Yep, it's our last day here.
咋了  这又不是我们的问题
What? It's somebody else's problem now.
我可不会坐在这把椅子上面
I wouldn't sit in that chair either.
好吧  我今天得有所作为
Well, I'm making today count.
我在转学之前打败亚蒂
I'm gonna take Artie down and leave the school
我想当无可非议的火箭大王
The undisputed rocket king.
祝你好运  熊孩子
Way to go, munch.
能被你激发灵感的人
You're an inspiration...
根本没有
To no one.
好吧
Okay.
今天是我们住在这里的最后一天了  你打算干什么
So what are you doing with your last day?
我还有一些事情要做
I've got a few loose ends to tie up.
你知道的越少越好
The less you know, the better.
或许我拉粑粑不关门
I might poop with the door open,
但是我还是有我自己的秘密
But I still have my secrets.
我一宿没睡  做了一个新的火箭
I stayed up all night building a brand-new rocket.
它很完美
It's perfect--
就连在舷窗里面挥手的外星人都有
Right down to the decal of the aliens waving in the windows.
各位好啊
Hi, guys.
如果今天是我在这里的最后一天
If I only have one day left here,
我得必须向迪吉表白了
I'm gonna tell Diggie how I feel about him.
我得直接看向他那双漂亮的
I'm going to stare right into those
棕色眼睛  说
Beautiful brown eyes and say
“迪吉  别来无恙”
“Diggie, s'up?"
我在这里的最后一天  我要想方设法说服我妈
For my last day, I'm gonna convince mom
我身体不舒服  想晚些走
That I'm sick so I can stay behind
和我儿时所住的地方告别
And say good-bye to my childhood home.
53 度
126.8.
我能活着已经是奇迹了
I'm lucky to be alive.
这就是不能在太空中用牙线的原因
And that's why you never floss in space.
好好想想
Think about it.
火箭爱好者们
Rocketeers,
大饱眼福吧
Feast your eyes
看看我的新火箭
On my new rocket.
名叫“亚蒂是怂包”
The "Artie is a wad-bag."
你不能给你的火箭这样命名
You can't call your rocket that.
那好  我已经做了不少火箭  亚蒂
Well, I've made a lot of rockets, Artie.
你能把它的名字大声说出来
Could you say the name out loud
好让我知道你在说哪一个么？
So I know which one you're talking about?
问得好
Nice try.
但你当我是傻瓜么
But do you take me for a fool?
不  我当你是怂包
No. I take you for a wad-bag.
是时候决出谁是火箭大王了
It's time we settle who the rocket king is
一劳永逸
Once and for all.
大声宣布你的挑战吧
Speak forth your challenge!
我现在就宣布
I'm speaking forth, baby.
鹰式 500 型
The falcon 500
对决“亚蒂是怂包”
Versus "Artie is a wad-bag"
走廊火箭对决赛
In a hallway rocket chair race.
我接受你的挑战
I accept your challenge.
等等  我们什么时候开始比赛
Wait, when are we doing this again?
我今天计划都快排满了
I'm a little overscheduled today.
3 点整怎么样
Like 3:00?
3 点半行吗
Does 3:30 work?
3 点半  喷泉边上见
3:30 by the water fountain.
- 是粘了口香糖的那个还是能工作的那个  -当然是能工作的那个了
- Or the one that works? - The one that works, duh.
- 但我刚才不知道啊  - 那么你现在知道了
- Well, I didn't know. - Well, now you do.
- 好吧  接受你的挑战  - 太好了
- Fine. Challenge accepted. - Great.
别了 亲爱的老房子
Goodbye, old house.
我们还并未互相重新了解
We just barely got to know each other again
就又被拆开了
And now we're torn apart.
沙发 你可能安抚我受伤的心灵
Will you comfort me, couch,
您这午后之梦
Collector of afternoon dreams
和零碎硬币的载体
And loose change?
老妈又要视频对话
facegabbing again, mom?
嘿 皮特 我是抱抱熊啊
Hey, pete. It's care bear.
我刚看到你经过走廊
I just saw you walk down the hall.
你那新牛仔裤看起来帅呆了
Those new jeans are looking good.
看来我不用装就已经病了
And now I don't have to pretend to be sick.
吾去也  彩色玻璃窗
Oh. Au revoir, stained glass window.
你让我的生活丰富多彩
You colored my world.
我还记得当我
I remember when I was--
帕克  你在这儿干嘛
Parker, what are you doing?
我在填我的隧道
I'm filling in my tunnels.
好吧  也许我该更具体一些
Okay, perhaps I should have been more specific.
什么
What?!
我在房子内部挖了一个
I've been digging an intricate
错综复杂的隧道网
Network of tunnels around the house.
起初  这只不过是用作逃离单调乏味的
At first, it was an escape from the monotony
每日生活
Of everyday life,
但最后就变成了个真实的逃离口
But then it became an actual escape
防患于未然嘛
In case stuff got real.
你在里面弄了一些神神秘秘的小玩意  对不
You've got a serious party going on up there, don't you?
嘿  幸亏这些隧道
Hey, thanks to these tunnels,
我可以只花三步
I can get from my bedroom
就从卧室跑到卫生间
To the bathroom in three steps.
- 哦  - 有时
- Oh. - Sometimes,
分秒必争
Every second counts.
我决定我应该给迪吉留张字条
I decided I should write Diggie a note,
但我想做点有纪念意义的事
But I wanted to do something memorable.
之前他把他的篮球落在了我家
And he left his basketball at my house,
所以我决定还给他
So I returned it
上面留了言  我喜欢你 - 麦蒂
With the words "I like you. - Maddie"
是笔写在上边的
Written on it.
咋了
What?
这是“疯狗鲁尼”最甜蜜的举动了
That's as sweet as mad dog Rooney gets.
呼  我得洗个澡  伙计们
Whoo! I gotta shower, guys.
我已经汗流浃背了
I'm sweating like a pig.
待会见  好不
I'll see you later, all right?
噢  麦蒂把篮球还给我了
Oh hey, Maddie returned my basketball.
很好
Okay.
他正在读留言
He's reading it.
哦天啊  她把球弄得脏兮兮的
Oh man, she got it all dirty.
别来无恙  迪吉
S'up, Diggie.
噢  嘿  鲁尼
Oh, hey, Rooney.
那啥
So,
我把篮球还给你了
I returned your basketball.
你看见上面有什么了没
Did you see what was on it?
哦  那些黑渍啊
Oh, that?
管他呢
Who cares?
什么
What?
对啊  没什么大不了的
Yeah, whatever.
又不是什么大事
It's not a big deal.
不是什么大事
Not a big deal?
对于我来说这算是最重要的事了
To me this was like the biggest deal ever.
好吧  跟你说
Yeah, you know what?
这彻头彻尾就是个错误
This was a mistake.
天啊  刚才发生了什么
Wow. What was that all about?
咋地  我就在走廊里自言自语
Yeah, I'm talking to myself in the hall.
刚才被妹子弄晕了  你爬开
Baffling girl moment. Move on.
听好了
All right.
绕大厅一周
Once around the hall.
胜者将永远被尊为
Winner is declared now and forever
火箭大王
The rocket king.
呼啦
Holla!
而输家将被贬为乔伊
And the loser is declared joey.
啊哈
Burn!
嘿  我们再添点赌注
Hey, how about we make things
让游戏更有趣怎么样？
Even more interesting?
允许胜者
Let's say the winner
公开羞辱输家
Gets to publicly humiliate the loser
整整一周
For an entire week?
他就自己乐去吧  不论输赢
Joke's on him because, win or lose,
下周我都在麦迪逊了
Next week I'll be in madison.
未来真美好
Future burn.
对的  明天他就会感觉到了
Yeah, he'll feel that one tomorrow.
就等着吃我的尾气吧
Get ready to eat my exhaust.
你永远抓不到猎鹰
You'll never catch the falcon.
你永远抓不住怂包
You'll never catch the wad-bag.
这就是怂包发出的声音
That's the sound a wad-bag makes.
哦  对了
Oh, wait.
你早就知道了怂包怎么叫了
You already knew that.
为啥今天你家人都这么不正常
Why is everyone in your family acting so weird today?
今晚鲁尼全家就要搬去麦迪逊了
The rooneys are moving to madison tonight.
你们搬家了  什么
You're moving? What?
对啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我也挺难接受的
I took it pretty hard myself.
但是既来之则安之嘛  迪吉
But you have to embrace it, Diggie.
不管怎样  如果万事都不改变
After all, if nothing ever changed,
就不会有纷飞的蝴蝶了
There would be no butterflies.
哥们  我也会想你的
Yeah, I'll miss you too, buddy.
好戏就要开场了
Let's light this candle.
当我看到其他的火箭爱好者
As I looked at my fellow rocketeers,
我意识到
I realized
一旦我成为了火箭大王
If I became rocket king
次日又离开
And left the next day,
要让谁来领导他们
Who would lead them?
我不得不让亚蒂胜出
I had to let Artie win.
他尽管是我的死对头
He was my nemesis,
但他也是社团最大的希望
But he was also the club's best hope.
喔！
Ooh!
输掉了比赛也摧毁了荣耀
Losing the race bruised my pride.
撞上了台阶也摧毁了我的肩膀
Smashing into the stairs bruised my shoulder,
我的膝盖
My knees
和我的腰子
And my kidney.
耶  万岁
Yeah! Whoo!
我赢了
I won.
我是火箭大王
I am the rocket king.
好好领导他们 怂包
Lead them well, wad-bag.
别辜负了我
Lead them well.
万岁  耶
Whoo! Yeah!
Were you just gonna move away without saying goodbye?
Well, I was gonna tell you,
But then I got really hurt
When you blew me off after reading my note.
The one that I wrote on the basketball,
Like one does when one is terrified
Of getting hurt,
Like one did.
I must have smudged it with my basketball pig sweat.
What did it say?
I like you, Diggie.
I like you too, Maddie.
( chuckles )
Coming through, people.
Tunnels don't fill themselves.
Ignore him. Stay focused.
Okay.
If you're moving,
I want you to have this.
And not because you're cold.
But because...
This means something to me.
Like you do.
Diggie!
I knew you'd come by.
Couldn't let your best pal leave town
Without saying goodbye, huh?
( clears throat )
( sighs )
I really like you, man.
Oh.
爸妈用来记录我们身高的门框
The doorjamb where mom and dad marked our heights.
我一直比玛蒂高一点点
I was always an eighth of an inch taller than Maddie,
那不算什么  但意义重大
Not that it matters... But it does.
听着
Listen up!
我们有重大消息要宣布
We have some big news.
玛蒂和迪吉正式
Maddie and Diggie are officially
承认互相喜欢对方
In like with each other.
你们俩总算告白啦
Finally.
玛吉配成真啦
The birth of Miggie.
呵  你别这样
Yeah, don't do that.
其实我有点喜欢这种称呼的
Aw, I kind of like it.
我不喜欢
I hate it.
你们俩成一对我其实很开心
I'm so glad you guys are finally together.
我受够了
This is too much.
我们不能搬家啊
I mean, we can't leave.
我们一辈子都住在这里的啊
Our entire lives are here.
我才不管爸妈的意见
I don't care what mom and dad say.
我就赖着不走了
I am staging a live-in.
谁愿意和我一起
Who's with me?
嘿  孩子们
Hey, kids.
看来你们都整理好行李了
So I see you guys have packed.
我们才不会让你们卖掉房子
We are not letting you sell the house
搬家去麦迪逊的
And move us to madison.
卖掉房子
Sell the house?
这是哪门子空穴来风
Where on earth did you get that idea?
还不是你们两个和我们打的可视电话
From when you facegabbed us.
我们听见你们两个的整个邪恶计划了
We heard your whole devious plan.
是啊
Yeah.
我还听见你评论老爸的新裤子
And I heard you talking about dad's new pants.
恶心
Gross!
你们这个老爸只要穿得稍微想点样子
When your father looks even remotely fashionable
我就得鼓励鼓励他
I have to encourage that.
是啊
It's true.
就像训练海狮那样
It's like training a seal.
其次
And second of all,
我不知道你们从可视电话
I don't know what you think you heard
都听见了些什么
On facegab,
我们不是要搬家去麦迪逊
But we are not moving to madison.
只是去度个周末
We're just going there for the weekend.
你的意思是说我白白的把我挖的隧道填了
You mean I filled in my tunnels for nothing?
隧道
Tunnels?
这下麻烦大了
Stuff just got real.
且慢
Wait.
照此说来我下周一还是得去学校
You're saying I have to go to school with Artie
和亚蒂抬头不见低头见的
On Monday?
我这就上楼整理行李去麦迪逊
I will be upstairs packing for madison...
然后闷头痛哭
And crying.
主要是闷头痛哭
Mostly crying.
你们干什么要把这一次旅行搞得这么神秘
Why were you keeping this trip such a secret?
好吧  我们还是把事情讲明了
All right. Might as well come clean.
除害专家要来熏一下我们家
Exterminators are tenting our house.
我们家有蛀虫
We're infested with beetles.
家里有虫子
Bugs?
等等  你们不能把那些虫子打掉
Wait. You can't exterminate the beetles.
那是我花了无数时间养出来的
I spent forever breeding those suckers.
你是这整件事的始作俑者
This whole thing is your fault?
别怪我  怪那些虫子
Don't blame me. Blame the beetles.
我这就去和它们好好谈谈
You know what? I'm gonna go have a word with them.
你赶紧给我从这个洞里面出来
Get out of that hole right now.
年轻人  我们得谈谈
We need to talk, young man!
我知道你在里面
We know you're in there.
我这就进来了
I'm going in.
哇
Wow.
既然如此
So...
看来你还是住在这里
Looks like you're staying.
我们两个有了这么一番对话
We've said some things.
是啊
We sure did.
看来我们之间一切都有所不同了
I guess things are gonna be different from now on?
是啊  我觉得
Yeah, I guess.
那么  别来无恙
So... S'up?
有点事
Stuff.
哈  怎样
Bam, what?
天
Whoa.
我是怎么到这里来的
How did I get here?
乔伊·鲁尼
Joey Rooney,
既然你在火箭竞速中败北了
As loser of the great rocket chair race,
就让公开羞辱开始吧
Let the public shaming begin.
你这一星期就得穿这个
You have to wear this all week.
记得注意别把衣服搞脏了  鲁尼
So remember to keep it clean, Rooney.
哎呀
Oops.
你的衣服上沾上巧克力咯
Chocolate burn.
免费的布丁可没什么可羞辱的
Well, there's no shame in free pudding.
一号隧道重新开张
Tunnel #1 reopened.